<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!--
This is not for human readers but for http://x28hd.de/tool/ 
--><x28map><topic x="190" ID="2" color="#eeeeee" y="192"><label><![CDATA[Zoom ?]]></label><detail><![CDATA[<html>
  <head>
    
  </head>
  <body>
    Sorry there is NO zoom in the web version. You may download the full version from here <a href="http://condensr.de">condensr.de</a>
    which is equally free.<br><br>To connect distant icons, move one closer 
    and put it back after drawing the line.<br><br>
  </body>
</html>
]]></detail></topic><topic x="40" ID="3" color="#ffbbbb" y="40"><label><![CDATA[Click this and look right]]></label><detail><![CDATA[Click an item on the left pane (canvas) to view its details on the right pane (here).<br /><br />It is a bit like turning cards face up in the game of Pairs (aka Memory or Concentration) -- just that it won't cost you scores. 'Turn' as often as you need.]]></detail></topic><topic x="40" ID="4" color="#d2bbd2" y="90"><label><![CDATA[Move]]></label><detail><![CDATA[To move an icon, drag it, i.e., press and hold the left mouse-button, move the mouse-pointer, and release the mouse-button.<br /><br />Do that to move similar items close to each other.]]></detail></topic><topic x="40" ID="5" color="#d2bbd2" y="140"><label><![CDATA[Connect]]></label><detail><![CDATA[To connect one icon to a second icon, you will ALT + drag it, i.e. <br />- point at the first icon, <br />- press and hold the ALT key, <br />- then drag the mouse until you reach the second icon,<br />- then release both the mouse-button and the ALT key.<br /><br />Exercise: Connect the 'ALT + drag' icon to some related icon.]]></detail></topic><topic x="40" ID="6" color="#d2bbd2" y="190"><label><![CDATA[Pan]]></label><detail><![CDATA[To pan the canvas, drag its background.<br /><br />Try it! Does it work?]]></detail></topic><topic x="40" ID="7" color="#bbbbff" y="240"><label><![CDATA[Drop input]]></label><detail><![CDATA[The easiest way to get your input into the map is <br />- to select some text in another window<br />- and just drag and drop it onto the canvas.<br /><br />Just try it. Don't be confused by the unexpected shapes of the mouse pointer -- once the mouse is over the canvas, it will change.<br /><br />Exercise: Select the two items below and drag them to the canvas: <br /><br /><pre>Item 1	demo
Item 2	demo</pre><br /><br />Now try text from a different window.]]></detail></topic><topic x="40" ID="8" color="#bbbbff" y="290"><label><![CDATA[Drop file(s)]]></label><detail><![CDATA[You may insert files just by dropping their icon(s) from your file explorer/ finder onto the canvas. Drop a simple text file, and each paragraph becomes an item. (For example, rough notes.)<br /><br />Or drop multiple smaller files, and they will all become separate items. (For example, some 'atomic' ideas from a notes app.)]]></detail></topic><topic x="40" ID="9" color="#bbbbff" y="340"><label><![CDATA[Add single items]]></label><detail><![CDATA[Right-click the canvas and select 'New item', then fill in the 'Label' and/ or 'Details' fields.<br /><br />Single icons are useful if you want to create 'towns' amidst the 'villages' on your thought map. But unlike categories, they don't even need a name!]]></detail></topic><topic x="40" ID="11" color="#bbffbb" y="390"><label><![CDATA[Save Map]]></label><detail><![CDATA[Right-click the canvas and select
'Save Map' to save it to the Download folder.<br /><br />Load it again later with right-click &gt; 'Load File(s)'.]]></detail></topic><topic x="40" ID="12" color="#ffff99" y="440"><label><![CDATA[Re-color]]></label><detail><![CDATA[Right-click an icon or a line, and select a new color.]]></detail></topic><topic x="190" ID="13" color="#d2bbd2" y="90"><label><![CDATA[Drag]]></label><detail><![CDATA[Drag an icon to move it. Drag the canvas background to pan.]]></detail></topic><topic x="190" ID="14" color="#d2bbd2" y="140"><label><![CDATA[ALT + drag]]></label><detail><![CDATA[ALT + drag an icon to connect it.]]></detail></topic></x28map>